nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいですね
Your smile is wonderful.
笑顔素敵ですね
now,
今、
I'm really nervous.
め っちゃ緊張してます
I see.
そうか
Well, first of all, uh...
じゃあ、ちょっと最初、 あの ね、
I asked if we could get along well, and I wanted to talk about the nervous part.
仲良くていいか、 緊張部分したいって、
Would you like to have a little chat?
ちょっとおしゃべりとかしませんか?
Good.
よいしょ
By the way, what do you usually do now?
ちなみに、今、 普段は、何をされている方ですか?
I'm a university student.
大学生です
Are you a university student?
大学生ですか?
That's right, you're young.
ですよね、若いっすね
Messed up.
め ちゃめちゃ
My stomach is also jiggling.
お腹もプルプルですしね
By the way, what year are you in university?
よちなみに、大学は何年生ですか?
I'm a first year university student.
大学1年生です
Well, if you're still old enough to drink alcohol,
じゃあ、まだ、お酒を飲める年では、
By the way, where are you going?
ちなみに、 どこに帰っていますか?
This is Aoyama.
青山です
Castle Peak?
青山?
Isn't this a really nice place?
めちゃめちゃいいとこじゃないですか?
But it looks good.
でも、いそうだね
I don't understand something.
俺、なんか分かんないんだ
Aoyama has an image of being cute.
青山って、可愛いってイメージなんだよね
Because it's so cute.
めちゃめちゃ可愛いから
It kind of looks good.
なんか、いそう
By the way, I'm sorry if this is normal, but
ちなみに、 普通で申し訳ないですけど、
It's really stylish.
めちゃめちゃスタイリーですね
The clothes are cute too.
服も可愛いね
Yeah.
うん
She was so cute, and her style was great too.
こんなにさ、可愛くてさ、 スタイルも良かった?
Can't you go?
行けんじゃない?
Miss Aoyama.
ミス青山
I can't go.
行けない
Can't go?
行けない?
You should definitely go.
絶対行けよって
Can I apply?
俺、応募していい?
Can I apply instead?
代わりに応募していい?
Aren't you embarrassed?
恥ずかしないですか?
I mean, aren't you interested in the entertainment world?
なんかさ、芸能界とか興味ない?
I think idols are cute.
アイドルとか、 可愛いなぁ、と思います
But no matter what I become, ah, don't you think so?
でも、自分がなろうと、 あ、 別にそう思わない?
It's a waste.
もったいないね
勉強勉強
I can't see it.
見る目ないね
The entertainment world.
芸能界がね
Do you go to any clubs or anything?
なんか、サークルとか行ってたりするんですか?
I haven't been there.
行ってないです
What kind of system are you studying?
どういう系勉強してるの?
For studies.
学にとか
In science and engineering.
理工学にね
Are you in science?
理系なんだ?
yes.
はい
It's a science major in Aoyama.
青山の理系なんだ
It's really good.
めっちゃいいじゃん
At Themis Aoyama.
テミス青山で
It's really good.
めちゃめちゃいいじゃん
Do you have a part-time job?
バイトとかしてるんですか?
My part-time job is at Saizeria.
バイトはサイゼリアでしてます
Saizeria?
サイゼリア?
Saizeria
サイゼリア
...
recommendation.
お すすめ
All recommended.
全部おすすめ
That's the only way to say it.
そう言うしかないよね
Can you tell me which Saizeria you work at?
どこのサイゼリアで働いてるまでは言えないですか?
Can't say that much?
そこまでは言えない?
He's coming.
来ちゃうもんね
Mainly me.
主に俺が
My hobby is visiting cat cafes.
趣味は、猫カフェ巡りですね
Visiting cat cafes?
猫カフェ巡り?
cute.
かわいい
Do you like cats?
猫好きなもん?
Please try meowing at least once.
一回じゃニャーってやってみてください
Meow?
ニャーって?
It's difficult.
難しいです
Meow?
ニャーって?
Meow.
ニャーって
Do you have a favorite type of cat?
好きな猫のある種類?
cheese.
チーズ
Sakyar?
サキャル?
cheese.
チーズ
Cheese is cute.
チーズかわいいね
Hana the cat over the dog?
犬より猫ハナ?
This is Neko Han.
猫ハンです
Do you visit cat cafes on your day off?
お休みの日は猫カフェ巡りしてるの?
yes.
はい
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏とかいるんですか?
I'm not there.
いないんです
Isn't it about as thick as it gets?
ボリぐらいないんですか?
About 2 years.
2年ぐらい
That's definitely it.
全然あれですね
I think I want something.
なんか欲しいと思ってますね
What if there is a good person?
いい人がいれば?
Isn't it before you go to bed?
寝る前にいるじゃないですか?
People think it's really cute.
めっちゃ可愛いと思われてる
A theme like Crimange.
クリマンジュみたいなテーマ
Do you know?
知ってる?
Crimange.
クリマンジュ
Cheeker too.
チーカーも
I understand.
わかります
I'm not currently in a club, but...
今サークルは入ってないってことなんですけど、
Originally, I was doing some lessons or something.
もともと何か習い事とか何かやってたりしました
Is it a lesson?
習い事ですか?
of the room.
部屋の
Did you do that?
やってたんですか?
How long have you been doing it?
どれくらいやってたんですか?
6 years of elementary school.
小学校の6年間
It's quite valuable.
結 構価値ですね
Can you play it by now?
今までに弾けるんですか?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Are there any songs you're good at?
何か得意な曲とか?
Nothing in particular.
特にないです
Piano, piano, if you can play the piano, even if you hate it?
ピアノ、ピアノ、ピアノ弾けたら嫌ってしても?
That's right.
そうなんです
It's a generation gap.
ジェネレーションギャップですね
Honestly, is it a match?
ぶっちゃけ一致なの?
As it is.
それなりに
You came here.
ここ来ちゃったもんね
It's not like I'm a camera now.
今さ、カメラになってるわけではさ、
I feel like I'm going to be in front of the camera from now on.
これからさ、カメラの前でって感じなんだけど、
Have you had such experience?
そういう経験ある?
It's my first time.
初めてです
first time?
初 めて?
By the way, I wish I could tell you.
ちなみに、言えたらでいいんだけどさ、
I think most of my social media is gone, though.
SNSとか多分なくしまってると思うんですけど、
Why today?
なんで今日?
I'm eating alone, but it's hard to eat alone.
私一人ごやししてるんですけど、 一人ごやしは大変で
Living alone as a student is difficult.
学生の一人暮らしは大変ですよね
Quite a bit.
なかなかね
You're paying for it yourself.
自分で払ってるんだよね
Living alone means you're in Koyama right now.
一人暮らしってことは、 今、小山ですよね
From where?
どこから?
This is Toyama.
富山です
Dabi girl from Toyama.
富山のダビ少女
I think you're already living alone.
なんか、 もう一人暮らしでされてると思うんですけど、
Don't you feel lonely being away from your family?
家族と離れて寂しくないですか?
I have been with my brother for a very long time,
私、お兄ちゃんとすごい長いんですけど、
I'm a little lonely.
ちょっと空き寂しいです
It's been a long time, brother.
長いんだ、お兄ちゃんと
She's a good sister.
いい妹じゃん
But, I'm going to be in front of the camera now.
でもさ、 今からカメラの前にね、
Don't worry.
すんじゃん
That or something
それとか
Well, this one is not distributed, right?
さ、 でもこれ、 配信しないやつですよね
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだけどね
Of course it is, but
もちろんもちろんそうなんだけど、
Fair enough.
まあまあ
That's right.
そうっすね
I'm just doing it as a hobby.
趣味でやってるだけなんて
Well then, you didn't talk much.
じゃあ、 あんまり喋ってもらえたからね
I'm nervous.
緊張します
緊張しますね
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いね
She's a beautiful girl.
美少女っすね
Would you like to go to the entertainment department?
芸能科行かないですか?
I'm not going to an arts school.
芸能科行かないです
A bob suits you a bit.
ちょっと ボブ似合うよね
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
My heart is beating now.
胸の鼓動今
What, what?
え、なになになに?
It's like my heart is beating in my chest.
胸の鼓動さ、確かみたいな
It's so exciting.
すごいハネてる
nervous
緊張して
Ru.
る
Is it not so good?
あ んまりいけないの?
Looks like I'll do my best.
頑張りそう
I'll do my best to take naughty photos.
エッチな撮影頑張りますって
エッチな撮影頑張ります
I'm addicted to it.
ハマい
What, what happened?
え、どうしたの?
Are you not ready yet?
まだ 心の準備できてないの?
It's cute though.
可愛いんだけど
It's just too cute, already...
ちょっとさ、 可愛すぎてさ、 もうさ、
This is how it turned out.
こんなんなっちゃってんだよ
He looks at me surprisingly.
意外に見てくれる
It's embarrassing, but I was really interested.
恥ずかしいけど、 本当に興味あったやつ
Do you understand?
分かる?
So, when you're ready to start,
じゃあ、 始めれそうになったら、
Go
ご
Well, tell me what you think about this day.
め んね、この一日感想言って
It's cute.
可愛いね
Look this way,
こっち向いてさ、
Looks cool.
カ ッコいいみたい
You have a small face, I mean, compare it to me.
顔ちっちゃいね、 てか、 俺と比較してみて、
Look.
ほら
It's about twice as different though.
倍ぐらい違うけど
what?
何?
What aren't you doing?
何してない?
I haven't done anything.
何 も してない
I'm looking for clothes.
服探ってんだ
picture?
え?
Lipopitor's?
リポピターの?
I just realized that,
今、気づいたんだけどさ、
This way it's easy to see.
こう やって見やすいように
It makes it easy to see.
見やすいようにしてくれてる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Look bigger than D...
Dより大きく見...
It feels big to the touch, though.
なんか、触った感じで大きいけどね、
From D.
Dより
Is it true?
本当ですか?
You won't know until you touch it.
もうちょっと、 触ってみないと分かるんだよね
You're nervous.
緊張してるね
Your legs and feet are beautiful.
足も、 足もきれいだね
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
This feels good.
気持ちいいこれ
Here, here, here, go, here, go.
ほら、ほら、ほら、いけ、ほら、いけ
Where are you touching now?
今、どこ触るの?
It's all about painting clothes.
あんまり、 服塗りからさ
Someone you can't see.
見えないやつか
I see.
なるほどね
You have a young face.
顔若いよ
Look closer.
近 くで見て
Armpit lick?
脇なめ?
I haven't seen it.
見てないよ
Look at the underwear.
下着の方で見て
Raise your hands and elbows up.
両手をさ、両肘上げて
Hold both elbows.
両肘持って
Don't want to watch Dora?
ドラ見たくない?
Sit down.
下座って
Where do you think you're looking right now?
今、どこ見てると思う?
yeah?
ん?
Have you ever seen my butt?
お尻見られたことある?
do not have.
ない
Not really.
ないね
Look a little rested.
ちょっと休んだ顔して
I'll do this.
やっちゃうよ、これ
Move your hands under your feet.
手も足の下から回して
This is so big, we're so entangled,
これさ、めっちゃなんかさ、 絡みついてさ、
The top is rough, but this...
上ザラザラしてるんだけどさ、 これ、
It's immunity.
免疫だね
The sound of the wind comes out.
風の音出んじゃう
When I put this in, the man went right away.
これ入れたら男の人すぐに行ってくれた
what?
なに?
It's on.
ついてんじゃん
It's still there after all.
や っぱりついてんじゃん
It's okay to have lots of lotion on.
ローションいっぱいついて、大丈夫
Since you gave me a blowjob earlier, I put a lot of horn lotion on you.
さっきフェラしてくれたから、 ツノローションいっぱいついて
Ru.
る
Try it.
やって みて
Didn't I tell you?
言ってなかったっけ?
Let's do it live.
生でやろう
Didn't you say that?
言 ってなかったっけ?
It feels better raw.
生の方が気持ちいいよ
生の方が気持ちいい
Should I give you a blowjob?
俺フェラしたらいい?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
Do you understand?
わかる?
Do you understand better live?
生の方がわかる?
Which feels better, rubber?
ゴムとどっちが気持ちいい?
Then, just lie down completely on your upper body.
じゃあ、 上半身だけ完全に倒れて
Only the upper body as betan.
ベタンとして上半身だけ
Now, raise your legs and put your hands between my legs.
じゃあ、足を上げて、 両 手を俺の足の間に入れて
Put your hands behind my back and between my legs.
両手を後ろに、 俺の足の間に入れて
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Sorry.
ごめんね
It felt so good.
気持ちよすぎて
Spread your legs.
足広げて
Shall I go to the sink?
私を流しに行こうか